kalooga.com 2007-11-02

# Privacy Policy

#### Privacy Policy

By using Kalooga search you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions outlined in the Terms of Service (TOS). The Kalooga Privacy Policy is part of the Kalooga TOS. Kalooga reserves the right to change it's Terms of Service and it's search service at any time without any notice or any liability to anyone. Changes will be put on the website with immediate effect.

Kalooga has a strict privacy policy, which aims to respect and protect the privacy of those that use Kalooga's search engine. Information which is identifiable as being information about you is not disclosed to any third party without first receiving your permission, except in cases where Kalooga is required to do so by a valid legal process. 

#### Cookies

Kalooga may use cookies. Cookies are used to collect data about trends and search patterns. Kalooga uses cookies to improve the level of service we provide. Kalooga will not disclose the cookies to third parties without first receiving your permission, except in cases where Kalooga is required to do so by a valid legal process. If you would like to prevent Kalooga from using cookies you can set your browser to refuse cookies. Please be aware that as result some parts of the service of Kalooga may not function properly. 

#### Sharing Information

Information is shared with business partners, advertisers and sponsors and similar third parties. However, the information shared regards only meta-information and does not include information, which holds your personal information. The information that may be shared includes for example how many times a certain key word is used for a search. It may also include visitor statistics. Other information is only provided to third parties in cases where Kalooga is required to do so by a valid legal process. 

#### What kind of Information?

Kalooga collects only information which does not directly refer to your personal information such as; email address, name etc., unless this information is willingly provided by you. Kalooga however does collect information about; browser language, IP address used for a query, browser type, and information on the linked searchresults that resulted in a visit. That information is used to improve our service to users. For example you may receive better searchresults or advertisments that are better shaped to meet your preferences. 

#### Links

Kalooga offers search result in the form of a link to webpages that are not controlled by Kalooga. These other sites may use cookies or other means to collect personal data from you. Kalooga is not responsible for such information-gathering or the use of this information. 

#### Questions?

Please feel free to contact us if you have any questions:

legal@Kalooga.com
